LINDY LIM

COMPUTER SCIENCE UNDERGRADUATE

CONTACT

+6587922875

Iindylimlw@gmail.com

wallflower6.github.io/portfolio

Singapore

SKILLS

Programming Languages (C / C++ / C# / Java / Python)

Web Development (HTML / CSS / JavaScript / Spring Boot / Flask / React JS / Three JS / D3 JS)

Game Development (Unity / Unreal / Construct3)

Cloud Computing (AWS)

3D Tools (Blender)

DevOps (Docker / GitLab / Kubernetes)

AI & ML Tools (Jupyter / NetLogo)

EDUCATION

BSc. Computer Science

Singapore Management University

2019-2023

- Recipient of the ASEAN Undergraduate Scholarship
- Undertook modules in Object-Oriented Programming, Backend Development, Cloud Computing, DevOps, Data Structures and Algorithms, Machine Learning, Linear Algebra
- Worked on projects with external clients such as Credit Suisse, COMO Club. and UBS Bank

AVAILABILITY

Available to work starting 2 May 2023

PROFILE

As a child who grew up filling exercise books with stories, I never thought I would find myself in computer science. It does make sense, however, considering the number of stories told and yet to be told through computing's own abstract brand of storytelling. Whether it is the next hit game to make players laugh and cry, web experiences to captivate users, or setting up infrastructure and streamlining processes to enable others to tell their stories, let me help your company weave that tapestry of code and logic.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Undergraduate Research Intern (Virtual Reality)

Singapore Management University

May 2022 - Aug 2022

- Lead the development of a Virtual Reality (VR) game in Unity Engine from concept to deployment based on client's requirements
- Collaborated with a supervisor / professor to architect project to ensure extensibility and modularity
- Wrote gameplay logic in C# for main gameplay functionality (ie. main menus, scoring system, AI for NPC behaviour, additional VR logic)
- Created and modified game assets in Blender, including materials, textures, and animations
- Deployed prototype application for Oculus Quest 2
- Prepared documentation and user guide for project

Developer Intern (Web & Games)

Big 3 Media, Singapore

May 2021 - Aug 2021

- Prototyped a 3D virtual tour for the web with ThreeJS
- Created AR experiences in SparkAR for potential commercial purposes
- Created and modified game assets in Blender for usage in AR projects
- $\bullet \;\;$ Wrote gameplay logic in C# for a character select menu for an upcoming game
- Prototyped simple point-and-click games with Construct 3
- Prototyped an exploratory panoramic webpage with Marzipano and JavaScript

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

Coding Mentor

Rails Girls Kuala Lumpur

Oct 2017 - Aug 2019

- Worked in a small team to organise a web development workshop with over 100 participants in collaboration with HERE Technologies
- Organised and prepared syllabus for a JavaScript workshop for 10 participants
- Volunteered as a coding mentor for Ruby on Rails at multiple workshops in Kuala Lumpur and London
- Introduced young children to programming during Hour of Code 2017

